# DICKY WAHYU PRATAMA SAPUTRA HIDAYAT

### Web Developer

Phone: +62 812 27976979
Email: dicky.wpsh@gmail.com
Website: https://dickywahyupra.github.io
Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dicky-wpsh/

#### **Profile**

I have had the experience as a fullstack web developer for 1.5 years in developing and programming websites and apps. I was able to work with the team and finish the project efficiently. I love technology, so I keep learning to keep growing

#### **Skills**

PHP, MySQL, PostgreeSQL, Codeigniter, Yii, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax, React JS, JSON, APIs, Rest API, HTML 5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Node JS, Linux.

## **Experience**

#### **Fullstack Web Developer**

August 2020 – Present CV. Diginet Media

- Designing, coding and developing E-Government software.
- Designing database MySQL, PostgreeSQL.
- Backend coding with Native PHP, Codeigniter, and Yii.
- Frontend with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax.
- Collaboration with QA.
- Troubleshooting any bug.
- Use GitLab.

#### **Administration Staff**

September 2017 – August 2020 CV. Diginet Media

- Creating a job progress report
- Participate in job tender (LPSE)
- Organize and execute assigned business projects
- Create a contract document

#### **Education**

#### Universitas Terbuka

2020 – Present Bachelor's Degree, Information System

# SMK Gema Nusantara Wonosobo (Vocational High School)

2014 –2017

Software Engineering